Count Felix von Luckner
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Count Felix von Luckner
2.3.10
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1641
- Count Felix von Luckner, 2.3.10
  - Lithograph print of the "Seeadler," faided comment and signature by Lowell Thomas [Count Felix von Luckner's ship], undated; 1; 10 x 14 color (Box 1641)
  - Lithograph print of the "Seeadler" [Count Felix von Luckner's ship], [21 copies], undated; 2; 10 x 14 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Verso: Count Felix Von Luckner sea raider "Sea Adler" - of First World War (German), 2-verso (Box 1641)
  - Lithograph print of the "Vaterland" [Count Felix von Luckner's ship], undated; 3; 10 x 14 color (Box 1641)
  - Watercolor painting of the "Mopelia" [Count Felix von Luckner's ship] by B.M. Webster, undated; 4; 16 x 20 color (Box 1641)
  - Charcoal lithograph print of a sketch of Count Felix von Luckner by McClelland Barclay, undated; 5; 15 x 13 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Lithograph print of a sketch of Count Felix von Luckner, 1928; 6; 10 x 8 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Count Felix Von Luckner with Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. [photograph], circa 1926-1928; 7; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Photograph of Felix von Luckner, close-up; inscription: Happy success because of [?] [?], Count v. Luckner 6/27, 1927; 8; 10 x 8 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Photograph of Count Felix von Luckner in profile, undated; 9; 14 x 11 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Felix von Luckner and his wife, Ingeborg, skiing, circa 1930s; 10; 9 1/2 x 12 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Countess Ingeborg Von Luckner, circa 1930s; 11; 14 x 11 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Countess Ingeborg Von Luckner, circa 1930s; 12; 14 x 11 b&w (Box 1641)
  - Countess Ingeborg Von Luckner, circa 1930s; 13; 14 x 11 b&w (Box 1641)